graphicmania.net 2014-11-22

# Privacy Policy - Graphic Mania

Your privacy is critically important to us. At Graphic Mania ( http://www.graphicmania.net ) we have a few fundamental principles:

  * We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it. (We can’t stand services that ask you for things like your gender or income level for no apparent reason.)
  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services. Like we might store information of User Behavior on our site so that we can tweak the User Interface of our site accordingly.
  * We aim to make it as simple as possible for you to control what’s visible to the public, seen by search engines, kept private, and permanently deleted.

Below is our privacy policy which incorporates these goals:

Like most website operators, Graphic Mania ( http://www.graphicmania.net ) collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Graphic Mania ( http://www.graphicmania.net )’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Graphic Mania ( http://www.graphicmania.net )’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Graphic Mania ( http://www.graphicmania.net ) may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Graphic Mania ( http://www.graphicmania.net ) also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. Graphic Mania ( http://www.graphicmania.net ) does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.

Certain visitors to Graphic Mania ( http://www.graphicmania.net )’s websites choose to interact with Graphic Mania ( http://www.graphicmania.net ) in ways that require Graphic Mania ( http://www.graphicmania.net ) to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Graphic Mania ( http://www.graphicmania.net ) gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. However, Graphic Mania (http://www.graphicmania.net ) does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

## Aggregated Statistics

Graphic Mania (http://www.graphicmania.net ) may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, Graphic Mania (http://www.graphicmania.net ) may monitor the User Behavior on http://www.graphicmania.net, like what visitors View, what they click on etc. Graphic Mania (http://www.graphicmania.net ) may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Graphic Mania (http://www.graphicmania.net ) does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

## Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

Graphic Mania (http://www.graphicmania.net) discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Graphic Mania (http://www.graphicmania.net)’s behalf or to provide services available at Graphic Mania (http://www.graphicmania.net)’s website, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Graphic Mania (http://www.graphicmania.net)’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them.

Graphic Mania (http://www.graphicmania.net) will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Graphic Mania (http://www.graphicmania.net) discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when Graphic Mania (http://www.graphicmania.net) believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Graphic Mania (http://www.graphicmania.net), third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an Graphic Mania (http://www.graphicmania.net) website and have supplied your email address, Graphic Mania (http://www.graphicmania.net) may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Graphic Mania (http://www.graphicmania.net) and our products.

We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Graphic Mania (http://www.graphicmania.net) takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

## Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Graphic Mania (http://www.graphicmania.net) uses cookies to help Graphic Mania (http://www.graphicmania.net) identify and track visitors, their usage of Graphic Mania (http://www.graphicmania.net) website, and their website access preferences. Graphic Mania (http://www.graphicmania.net) visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Graphic Mania (http://www.graphicmania.net)’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Graphic Mania (http://www.graphicmania.net)’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here.

## Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Graphic Mania (http://www.graphicmania.net) may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Graphic Mania (http://www.graphicmania.net)’s sole discretion. Graphic Mania (http://www.graphicmania.net) encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
